<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="7F62E391-C946-4D8D-8BE6-65AFC6BECDAE">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20110312" date="2011-03-12 22:11:30 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Spring Term Social</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>FunKoLoGy Spring Term Social</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Sunday, February 27, 2011</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="27_FunKoLoGy_Spring_Term_Social_files/shapeimage_1.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="420px" height="104px"/>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>The highly anticipated hip hop showcase has been confirmed and FunKoLoGy is going to catch it together as a society! We have 20 subsidized tickets @ 8 pounds each to this year&#x2019;s Serious About StreetDance (SAS). Interested people should email &lt;a href="mailto:evaf.flying@gmail.com"&gt;evaf.flying@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; and the first 20 people will get their tickets! Do not miss out on this opportunity of an evening of high energy fun!&#xD;&#xD;&#x201C;SAS is notably the UK&#x2019;s leading street dance showcase featuring the UK and Europe&#x2019;s most innovative and elite street dance companies and solo artists. The next event is confirmed on Sunday 27th February 2011 for one night only! &#xD;&#xD;The event includes some of the biggest names in street dance and performers who are undoubtedly the finest within their field. Launched in January 2009 by Kymberlee Jay, SAS is an unforgettable experience of street dance culture - feel the excitement of live entertainment from renowned performers in an unparalleled show of breathtaking proportions. SAS 2011 takes place at the indigO2 venue in London&#x2019;s state of the art O2 in the Docklands.&#xD;&#xD;Already acknowledged as the definitive street dance platform in the UK, with exclusive and explosive performances from some of the most spectacular talent, Serious About StreetDance is unmissable and is sure to be the most talked about street dance event of 2011.&#x201D;&#xD;&#xD;For more information visit: &lt;a href="http://www.seriousstreet.com"&gt;www.seriousstreet.com&lt;/a&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
